Maybe we'll start over here.
Would any of you like to say something?
Feel free.
You can say it in front of a fine group of people,
also journalists and reporters.
Would you want to start?
Sure.
Go ahead.
Absolutely.
President Trump, members of the cabinet,
really appreciate you guys bringing this together.
And the fact that we are here today and on such short notice
shows how serious you guys are taking
this issue of trans-terrorists and, frankly,
the cities and police departments
that are cooperating with Antifa, such as Portland.
I mean, the Portland politicians are literally
willing to sacrifice their own citizens just
to appease these Antifa terrorists.
It's sickening.
I've seen it firsthand, obviously.
When I went to jail that night, never expected it to happen.
I thought that they were maybe removing me for my own safety.
It never crossed my mind that I was
the one that was being arrested for a crime
after I was just thrown into a hole.
I heard from the Department of Homeland Security
after I had gotten out of jail, and one of your,
I won't say exactly who it was, but somebody very close
to Secretary Noem over here, said
that they were legitimately worried for my safety
in the Portland jail.
But luckily, the Portland jail was,
I was the only one there, essentially,
because they don't actually arrest people
in Portland, besides conservative journalists,
I guess.
So look, I'm glad that it was not a good night for me.
Let's just say that.
It was not fun sitting in that jail.
But I'm glad to see what has come of it.
And I've been able to talk to a bunch of FBI agents,
ATF agents, DHS agents that I didn't even
know existed until I went there and went to that ICE facility.
And the morale is at an all-time high.
It is so exciting to see these guys know now
that they have the backing of the Secretary, the DOJ,
as well as the President of the United States.
And they are there to do their job.
They are going to fulfill this mission
and deport these violent criminals.
I believe one of the ones that I did a ride along with Secretary
Noem yesterday, President Trump, and there
was a pedophile that had come into the country five times
over the past seven years.
Seven years.
And apparently under the Biden regime,
that was just allowed to happen.
That was fine.
No problem.
It's concerning to me that you're
seeing the Portland Police Department, as well
as the governor of Oregon, and the mayor, of course,
coming out and running defense for pedophiles
that have entered the country illegally five times.
It's crazy.
I'm glad it's taking a front row seat in the media.
And they're being forced to talk about it in reality,
because we are the ones that were on the ground.
We're the ones that are actually reporting what's going on.
And much of the legacy media has been either ignoring it
or covering for Antifa for years now.
So thank you guys so much for taking this seriously.
And President Trump, you mentioned that flag.
Remember, you put out a truth right after I took this flag
from that man that was burning it in the street.
Do you know who he is?
Oh, yeah.
I know exactly who it is.
So why don't you give it to Pam, give it to the attorney general,
and let's start prosecutions.
Yeah.
I actually have a second flag that he tried to burn, as well.
So I have two of them from the same guy.
Well, you also saw what happened when that flag started burning.
Everyone went crazy.
And that's when it started, when they started burning the flag.
So thank you.
If you could give the information,
it would be great.
Absolutely.
And at least that horrible night made you famous.
He was already famous.
I got a text from the president of the United States,
so I appreciate that.
And President Trump, after that happened to Nick,
I called Harmeet Dhillon.
And we opened a pattern and practice investigation
into the Portland police, very publicly,
as to how they let this happen.
Thank you, sir.
Mr. President, you're going to, Brandi Cruz,
you're going to hear us be very fired up today.
And you can tell.
And it's because some of us have been covering Antifa
for 15 years and have never had anyone
in a position of authority even acknowledge their existence.
I'll also tell you that I think that, had you not done,
the single most powerful thing you've
done to deal with this scourge has been acknowledging
that Antifa is a real thing.
I genuinely believe there would be people at these tables who
would be dead today and would have been killed in Portland,
had you not called them a terror organization
and said, we're going to bring the full weight
of the federal government to bear.
I talked to Katie Davis Court in Portland the other day.
She'd been assaulted all summer.
And she said the same thing.
They didn't see him as quick to violence as soon
as you made that designation.
So they're thinking in their heads.
They're worried.
There's been two dozen or so arrested in Portland.
They don't want to go to federal prison.
There's this video of them, one of them
who was in the face of an ICE agent.
And then he's in custody shaking.
Once you take the mask off, they're nothing.
I was told by probably a dozen people
not to tell you this.
I'm going to tell it to you anyway,
because it's relevant to what we're talking about.
I'm living proof that you can recover from TDS.
I had strong Trump derangement syndrome for probably
eight years.